https://www.shannonmiller.com/privacy-policy

MenuAboutAbout Shannon MillerAbout Shannon Miller Partners & Programs CloseBlog & EventsGymnasticsLatest Gym NewsVideosGymnastics How To CloseLifestyleHealth & NutritionNutritionRecipesHealth & WellnessCompeting With CancerFitnessFitnessWorkout VideosMotherhoodPregnancyMotherhood CloseProfessional SpeakingVideosFoundationShannon Miller Foundation CloseShopContact
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 1, 2010
Introduction: At Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC. (owner of ShannonMillerLifestyle.com) we realize the importance of feeling safe online and are fully committed to ensuring that your privacy is respected and protected. Our Privacy Policy below outlines the type of information we collect and receive from you.
PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE FOR SHANNONMILLERLIFESTYLE.COM CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO SUCH PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE.
1. How Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC. collects information
A. Personal Data you provide to Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC
Personally Identifiable Information is any information that can be used to identify a specific individual such as your name, email address, home address, and phone number. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC asks you to provide Personally Identifiable Information in various places. Some of these areas where the collection of such information takes place are listed below:
Email Newsletters
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC offers electronic newsletters. If you subscribe to any of these newsletters, you will be required to provide a valid email address as well as any other information that is relevant to the delivery of the newsletter.
Surveys and Polls
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC offers online surveys and questionnaires that ask users for opinions on various issues and/or other information. Occasionally, we may request demographic information (like zip code, age or gender) when you answer a survey. Such surveys are completely voluntary.
Sweepstakes and Contests
We may, on occasion, operate sweepstakes, contests and giveaways at ShannonMillerLifestyle.com. We typically ask you for your email address and/or phone number (to notify you if you’ve won, or not). We also ask for first and last names, and sometimes post office addresses in order to verify the entrant’s identity. In some situations, we need additional information as part of the entry process, such as a prize selection choice.
ECommerce Transactions
When you engage in an ecommerce transaction on ShannonMillerLifestyle.com you may be asked to provide credit card information and other Personally Identifiable Information in order to complete the transaction.
Health Information
In order to use some of the tools and services on the ShannonMillerLifestyle.com pages you may be asked to provide information about your health. When you provide this information, in certain circumstances Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC will associate it with Personally Identifiable Information.
B. Information gathered by Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC and its third party service providers
When you visit ShannonMillerLifestyle.com and interact with the services and tools that reside there, Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC and third parties with whom Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC has contracted to provide services to Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC may collect information on your actions. This type of information is generally collected from two sources. One is from the server log files and the other is from cookies.
IP Address
Your IP address is a number that is assigned by your ISP (Internet Service Provider) to your computer to identify its location. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also sometimes use IP addresses to communicate with members and subscribers and possibly even ban those members who are not complying with our Terms of Use.
Cookies
Our site uses a feature of your browser to set a “cookie” on your computer. Cookies are small packets of information that a site’s computer stores on your computer. The Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC Network can then read the cookies whenever you visit the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC websites. We use cookies to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to deliver content specific to your interests, to track the pages you’ve visited and to make sure you don’t see the same ads repeatedly. These cookies allow us to use the information we collect to customize your ShannonMillerLifestyle.com experience so that your visit to ShannonMillerLifestyle.com is as relevant and as valuable to you as possible.
You may modify your browser preference to provide you with choices relating to cookies. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies you may be unable to use those ShannonMillerLifestyle.com services that require registration in order to participate or will have to sign in each time you visit ShannonMillerLifestyle.com.
2. How Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC uses Information it collects
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC uses the information you provide for several purposes, such as to communicate with you and to give you a better experience when visiting ShannonMillerLifestyle.com by personalizing tools, content, services and email messages. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC also uses this information to build new services and develop offers that Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC believes are more relevant and valuable to you.
The information collected by Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC is also used to create aggregated portraits of the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC audience, portraits which present anonymous statistical demographic information but no personally identifiable information. This aggregated information is used, among other things, to determine trends and needs, and also to supply market research to potential advertisers and partners to help them understand who the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC audience is.
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC offers the ability to forward an article to another person via email. If you use this service, we will use the recipient’s email address in order to send the article or postcard and we will also ask for your email address. We do not use the recipient’s email address for any other purpose unless such recipient gives us permission to do so.
3. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to Third Parties
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC does not sell or otherwise share Personally Identifiable Information with unaffiliated third parties without your consent (please see the Opt-In/Opt-Out Policy below), except in the following instances: (i) disclosure is required by applicable law or pursuant to a court or similar order; (ii) as deemed necessary, in Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC’s discretion, to protect the legal rights or the property of Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC, a member or third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or (iii) in the event of a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or stock of Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC or its affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). In addition, Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC may provide Personally Identifiable Information to third parties who are providing technical or fulfillment services on behalf of Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC when such disclosure is required in order to provide those services, provided that such third parties agree to be bound by Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC’s Privacy Policy. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC also reserves the right to share any Personally Identifiable Information or other information about you which you provide to (or which is gathered from) ShannonMillerLifestyle.com with any or all of its subsidiaries and affiliates (subject to the opt-out right described below, with respect to disclosures of Personally Identifiable Information to Affiliates for their direct marketing uses).
Oftentimes, sweepstakes and contests offered on the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC Network are sponsored by unaffiliated third parties. Information that you provide as part of an entry into a sponsored sweepstakes or contest will be shared with the sponsor if we advise you of such in the sweepstakes rules. Most sweepstakes and contests will also ask you to consent to the release of information contained within the entry form for tax purposes if you become a winner. You should carefully review the rules of each sweepstakes, contest and giveaway which you enter as they may contain additional important information about Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC’s or a sponsor’s use of your personally identifiable information. To the extent that you wish to avail yourself of the health, wellness and medical related services and tools available through ShannonMillerLifestyle.com, Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC will be required to share certain personally identifiable information with the health, wellness and medical partners you have chosen to interact with. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC will use commercially reasonable efforts to contractually require all such third party advertisers and partners to agree to abide by the terms of this Privacy Policy.
The information you provide on pages of ShannonMillerLifestyle.com that are co-branded with a third party (including tools that are hosted by a third party) may be shared with advertisers and partners on an aggregated basis and in these instances your permission will not be requested since no Personally Identifiable Information will be shared or provided to these third party sponsors or advertisers. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC will, however, use commercially reasonable efforts to contractually require all such third party advertisers and partners to agree not to use any non-personally identifiable information about you, in conjunction with other sources of information, or otherwise, to identify you.
4. The Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC Opt-in/Opt-out Policy
From time-to-time, you may be asked to indicate whether you are interested in receiving information from us about special offers or news. If you do choose to receive these communications by means of an opt-in, we will occasionally send you an email message that matches your request(s). We currently provide the following opt-out opportunities:
At any time, you can follow a link provided in every newsletter or email message (except for e-commerce confirmation or service notice emails) to unsubscribe from that mailing list or email service.
Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, please note that Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC reserves the right to contact you in the event of a change in the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.
If you have additional questions about how one of our advertisers, partners or sponsors use information about you, we urge you to contact them directly. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “opt-in” is generally defined as any affirmative action by an Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC member or visitor to submit or receive information, as the case may be.
5. Guidelines regarding children
Personal information about children is a concern for all of us at Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC, we take the protection of children’s privacy very seriously. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC does not encourage participation or visitation by children. Visitors who are known to be under the age of 13 are prohibited from becoming a member.
6. How we protect and secure your information
Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC has numerous security measures in place to protect you from the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including your credit card information if you choose to conduct an e-commerce transaction on ShannonMillerLifestyle.com. All ecommerce transactions require use of your password. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC uses industry-standard tools, such as firewalls, to ensure that your information is secure and confidential.
7. Applicable Law
We control and operate ShannonMillerLifestyle.com from the United States. Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Please note that we do not represent or warrant that ShannonMillerLifestyle.com is appropriate for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access ShannonMillerLifestyle.com do so at their own initiative and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.
8. Changes to this Privacy Policy
We will notify our members when we make any significant changes to our Privacy Policy that affect the use of any personally identifiable information we collect. We will not make new use of any Personally Identifiable Information which Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC gathered from individual members or visitors prior to any such significant change in our Privacy Policy without first obtaining the member’s or visitor’s consent for any new uses. In instances where we ask for your Personally Identifiable Information and we tell you the data we are collecting on that page will be shared with unaffiliated third parties, and in cases where a member, visitor or subscriber to ShannonMillerLifestyle.com opts-in to share his/her information with third parties, those disclosures and opt-ins will override anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy. In addition, Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC reserves the right to make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that will not affect Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC’s use of a user’s Personally Identifiable Information at any time without any notice to you other than posting any such changes in a revised Privacy Policy on the Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC Network. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to be sure you are familiar with the most current version. The Privacy Policy will include the most recent date in which any revision has been made. Please note that this Privacy Policy is also incorporated into Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC’s Terms of Use.
9. Contact information
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or anything else about Shannon Miller Enterprises, LLC or ShannonMillerLifestyle.com you can contact us.
Recent Posts
Shannon Miller Receives AKTIV Against Cancer Award
Shannon Miller Joins The Eve Awards
The Gold Medal Mindset to Overcoming Cancer
Lessons from the Olympics Helped Shannon Miller Fight Ovarian Cancer
US Gymnast Shannon Miller Chosen As Event Ambassador for Mumbai Marathon
Web Design and Marketing
